Who's there?
Did you just
see a child?
No.
I'm fine.
The thing is, did you guys
really not see that kid just now?
We really didn't.
You were just talking to yourself.
Who's there?
How long have you had this eye condition?
Ever since I barely
escaped the fire at the library pavilion,
I noticed my eyes
were different from normal people's.
Huai'er, run!
Run!
What's wrong with my master's eyes?
I'm not a doctor.
I can't tell much from this.
Maybe it's just from lack of sleep,
causing mild redness.
That wouldn't cause hallucinations, right?
He always sees those weird things.
Did heaven open his Third Eye?
Is he hallucinating?
Don't talk nonsense.
What hallucinations?
If you ask me,
he either has an eye problem,
or a brain problem.
But it's fine.
Once you solve the case,
I'll take you to the provincial hospital.
It's all over. It's all over.
Only four hours until dawn.
And we haven't even pinned down a suspect.
What do we do?
That's right.
Don't worry.
As soon as the sun comes up,
Father will report to the chief,
and marry you off in grand style.
Mengzhu died from a Puppet Hidden Weapon,
and the First Madam died from tea
laced with deadly oleander poison.
It seems the killer
knows everyone in Li Mansion inside out.
And this puppet that keeps appearing,
I keep feeling
that someone is intentionally
trying to tell us something.
Madam,
the wedding ceremony is tomorrow morning.
There's no time to get new wedding shoes.
These were left by the Second Madam.
See if they fit you first.
Just leave them there for now.
Um,
how did the Second Madam die?
The Second Madam...
she broke the Demon-Revealing Mirror,
and was haunted by an evil spirit.
A Demon-Revealing Mirror?
After the First Madam died,
the Master, to drive off the Flower Demon,
hired a Spirit Medium to perform a ritual.
Insolent Flower Demon!
There's nowhere to hide!
Spirit Medium,
Are you sure there's a Flower Demon here?
Absolutely certain.
Look at this compass spinning wildly.
The demonic aura in the mansion is heavy.
We must eliminate the demon immediately,
or the Flower Demon will cause havoc
and harm others.
Then hurry up and think of a way!
First, I'll perform an exorcism ritual,
then install a Demon-Revealing Mirror,
and set up a Warding array.
A Demon-Revealing Mirror?
Hang the Demon-Revealing Mirror up here,
and demons will reveal their true forms.
It also wards off evil and expels ghosts.
Remember,
you must never break this mirror.
Otherwise, if my Warding array is broken,
the Li Mansion will be in danger.
The Second Madam studied abroad.
Not only did she like her bedroom
decorated in a Western style,
she also didn't believe in superstitions.
Second Madam, you mustn't!
You absolutely mustn't, Second Madam!
I'm so sick of this superstitious junk!
Don't break it!
Second Madam!
She broke the Demon-Revealing Mirror,
and the Spirit Medium's Warding array.
Ever since then,
the disasters started.
It's the Flower Demon.
The Flower Demon is back!
Didn't she just break a vase?
How is that related to the Flower Demon?
The broken vase...
...was just the beginning of the disaster.
After breaking the Demon-Revealing Mirror,
inside her room,
strange things kept happening.
Which of these two colors looks better?
They both look good on you.
In a couple of days,
I'll take you out to buy some new jewelry.
Master!
Are you okay?
Let me help you up.
The furniture would break inexplicably,
and strange noises were heard at night.
What's wrong?
It's getting late.
Let's go to sleep.
Since disasters kept happening in her room,
he hired a Spirit Medium for feng shui.
Lord Lao commands me to slay demons.
Granting me divine methods,
what demon dares not submit?
What ghost dares to stand in my way?
Bold demon!
Show your true form at once!
Spirit Medium,
what exactly is wrong with this room?
There's a wicked presence.
Master,
there's demonic energy in this room.
The demon is coming for the Second Madam.
Right at this moment,
it is right above this crystal chandelier.
The crystal chandelier?
A thousand-year-old Flower Demon
fancies Madam's Western crystal chandelier.
To gather the Crystal's spiritual essence
to cultivate its dark arts
and slaughter everyone!
Slaughter everyone?!
Somebody!
Take down this crystal chandelier now!
Stop!
Fine!
Let's see who dares to touch my chandelier!
Madam!
I'll fight him!
Madam,
this chandelier has demonic energy!
This crystal chandelier of mine
was specially shipped back from France!
It's priceless!
I doubt my chandelier has demonic energy,
it's you who has it, Spirit Medium!
Making up Flower Demons to scare people.
I've absolutely had enough!
Alright, Madam.
Calm down, calm down.
If you dare to take down my chandelier,
I'll beat you up too!
Okay, okay! We won't take it down!
As long as you like it,
you can have any chandelier you want.
It's one o'clock.
I was to meet the Master to try on suits.
Why isn't he back yet?
Chunmei!
Coming, coming!
Go and see if the Master is back yet.
Yes, Madam.
The Flower Demon killed someone!